### STEFANO ESPOSITO

#### Master's graduate in Artificial Intelligence and Robotics



#### **EDUCATION**

Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence and Robotics

#### University "La Sapienza"

Thesis title: Real-Time Path-Tracing of Implicit Neural

Representations. Final mark: 110/110.

#### Research experience

#### IVC, Hochschule Bonn-Rhein-Sieg

# Oct 2020 - Feb 2022

P Bonn, Germany

Two Erasmus semesters working on my master's thesis research project in the *neural rendering* group.

# Bachelor's degree in Computer Science University "La Sapienza"

Rome, Italy

Thesis title: Obtaining a 3D bas-relief from an image using Inverse Rendering techniques. Final mark: 110/110 cum laude.

## High School diploma in Computer Science I.I.S. Luigi di Savoia

m Sept 2011 - July 2016

Chieti, Italy

Final mark: 100/100.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Research Associate

#### IVC, Hochschule Bonn-Rhein-Sieg

May 2022 - Ongoing

**♀** Bonn, Germany

Full-time position.

### Computer Science Tutor (DUA)

Villa Nazareth Servizi S.r.l

**2017 - 2020** 

Rome, Italy

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

 S. Esposito, D. Baieri, S. Zellmann, A. Hinkenjann, E. Rodolà. KiloNeuS: Implicit Neural Representations with Real-Time Global Illumination. Preprint on ArXiv. Jun 2022.

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a master's degree researcher with a strong passion for broad and ever-expanding fields such as deep learning, computer graphics and their intersection. I consider myself an educated programmer and a true technology enthusiast; in my spare time I like to learn new things, keep up-to-date with what is happening in the world and to connect with nature by pushing myself on tough but beautiful hikes through high mountains.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **University College of Merit admission**

₩ Sept 2016

Rome, Italy

Admission to the Villa Nazareth University College of Merit of the Domenico Tardini Foundation.

#### **CMMRS Pre-doctoral School admission**

# 1-6 Aug 2022

♀ Saarbrücken, Germany

Attendee at Cornell, Maryland, Max Planck Pre-doctoral Research School: "Emerging Research Trends in Computer Science".

#### **STRENGTHS**

Reliable Self-motivated Problem solving
Motivator Teamwork Meticulous
Determined Open minded
Python PyTorch OpenCV C++ CUDA OpenGL LaTeX Matlab Java
Deep Learning Computer Graphics
Computer Vision Robotics Math Algorithms

#### **LANGUAGES**

Italian
Native speaker

English
Fluent, C1 Level

German
Basics, A1 Level

